<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bulletjournalist - ideas, inspiration, and insights for your bullet journal</title>
    <description>ideas, inspiration, and insights for your bullet journal</description>
    <link></link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Spread Idea: Makeup Inventory</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;2016 has been been about paring down my possessions, partly inspired by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/gp/product/1607747308/ref=as_li_qf_sp_asin_il_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;tag=sdw00-20&amp;camp=1789&amp;creative=9325&amp;linkCode=as2&amp;creativeASIN=1607747308&amp;linkId=92ea5913843dec6b1b7b0764b57c0c72&quot;&gt;The Life-Changing Magic of Tidying Up&lt;/a&gt;, a popular book that makes a great case for why we can be happier living with less things. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;center&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/makeupinventory.jpg&quot; width=250px style=&quot;border: solid 2px black&quot;&gt;&lt;/center&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the places where I had too much stuff is in my makeup collection. Inspired by years of watching beauty gurus, I had let my makeup collection grow to a size that was too much for me. Inspired by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tV0N7FvXRVI&quot;&gt;this series of videos&lt;/a&gt;, I decided to track my makeup collection in an inventory spreadsheet to see how I was doing with a gradual makeup declutter (I know it’s not the method recommended by Marie Kondo in her book, but this is what worked for me. )&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2016 08:27:31 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>/spread%20ideas/minimalism/2016/11/21/makeup-inventory/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/spread%20ideas/minimalism/2016/11/21/makeup-inventory/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello all, welcome to bulletjournalist.com! I plan to write short, quick posts about my spread ideas, spread layouts, and many other things related to journaling. I started bullet journaling in early 2016 after seeing &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=EAk_ZusrRJQ&quot;&gt;this video&lt;/a&gt; and being inspired. Now, I use my bullet journal to plan out my life, make sure I’m making progress toward all my goals, and to help my forgetful self plan things out. Thanks for checking out my blog! I hope it inspires you in some way.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2016 08:27:31 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>/chatty/2016/11/15/welcome/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/chatty/2016/11/15/welcome/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
